http://www.bigdecision.co.uk/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy // Big Decision
Skip to contentHomefacebooktwitterBusiness as Usual 01899 438088 |hello@bigdecision.co.uk
Search for:
Who We AreWhat We DoWebsite ProductionWeb DesignContent DrivenUser Experience Design (UX)Content Management SystemsMethodsEcommerceDigital MarketingContentEmail MarketingPaid SearchSearch MarketingSocial MediaMoreWeb HostingDomain NamesEmailOur WorkGet in TouchPrivacy PolicyHome/Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy.Big Decision is committed to complying with the General Data Protection Regulation. Your privacy is very important to us and we want you to be confident that your personal data is kept safely and securely and to understand how we use it to offer you a better service.We have published this notice to help you understand how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use our website www.bigdecision.co.uk; also any other personal information that you may provide to us when we provide you with our services. Please take a moment to read this Privacy Policy so that you will understand how we use your personal information.If we make changes to this notice we will notify you by updating it on our website.Who We AreBig Decision provides high-quality web sites, web development, digital marketing and other online services to small and medium-sized businesses.The Information We CollectWhen you sign up to our newsletter or contact us using our contact form, we collect the personal information you give us such as: your name address email address information on how you use the site, using cookies and page tagging techniques how you use our emails – for example whether you open them and which links you click on when you browse our website, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating systemEmail marketingWith your permission, we may send you emails about our services, products and news updates. We use Mailchimp for email marketing and to communicate with our clients. Mailchimp offers a double opt-in service and offers full visibility of any of your information used by this service and the option to unsubscribe which will delete any of your personal data.We do not have an expiry on the amount of time we will hold your data for. We do offer withdrawal of consent and deletion of your data at any time upon your request.Payment detailsIf you choose to pay your invoices via our website your credit card details or payment details from PayPal will be collected. We use these to process your payment, we will not be able to take payment online if these details are not provided. You can opt to pay your invoices via online banking or by post.Why We Need ItWe use Google Analytics software to collect information about how you use www.bigdecision.co.uk. We do this to monitor how people interact with our website and to help make sure the site is meeting the needs of its users. Google Analytics stores information about: the pages you visit how long you spend on each page how you got to the site what you click on while you’re visiting the siteWe do not collect or store your personal information (for example your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.We also collect data in order to: improve the site by monitoring how you use it gather feedback to improve our services, for example our email alerts respond to any feedback you send us, if you’ve asked us to send email alerts to users who request themConsentHow do you get my consent?When you provide us with personal information to complete an enquiry, we require your acceptance of the content of this privacy policy, that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.How do I withdraw my consent or request my data to be removed?If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to store any personal data about you, contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at hello@bigdecision.co.uk or mailing us at: 1 Biggar Business Park, Market Road, Biggar, Lanarkshire, ML12 6FX.What We Do With Your DataWe will share your data if we are required to do so by law – for example, by court order, or to prevent fraud or other crime.We will not: sell or rent your data to third parties share your data with third parties for marketing purposesData SecurityOur website is hosted by United Hosting Services. Data is stored through United Hosting Services data storage, databases and the general hosting application. They store your data on a secure server protected by a firewall.PaymentAny payments for invoices are processed via Paypal. Please take the time to read their privacy policy.Data breachesIn the rare occurrence of a data breach, which would significantly harm individuals, we will be report it within 72 hours to the ICO. We will also notify any customers affected.Third Party ServicesIn general, the third-party service providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.Once you leave our website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy.Links to Other WebsitesWhere we provide links to websites of other organisations, this privacy notice does not cover how that organisation processes personal information. Please read the privacy notices on the other websites you visit.Retention of Personal DataWe will only retain your personal data for as long as: it is needed for the purposes set out in this document the law requires us toIn general, this means that we will only hold your personal data for a minimum of 1 year and a maximum of 7 years.CookiesCookies are small text files that are placed on your machine to help the site provide a better user experience. In general, cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for things like shopping carts, and provide anonymised tracking data to third party applications like Google Analytics.These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. View our Cookie Declaration or to opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Some cookies are necessary to allow you to browse our website, use its features, and access secure areas. The use of these cookies is essential for the website to work. For example, we use user-input cookies for the duration of a session to keep track of a user’s input when filling in forms that span several pages.You may prefer to disable cookies on this site and on others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the Help section of your browser or taking a look at the About Cookies website which offers guidance for all modern browsers.Your RightsYou have the right to request: information about how your personal data is processed a copy of that personal data that anything inaccurate in your personal data is corrected immediatelyYou can also: raise an objection about how your personal data is processed request that your personal data is erased if there is no longer a justification for it ask that the processing of your personal data is restricted in certain circumstancesIf you have any of these requests, get in contact with us at hello@bigdecision.co.uk or call 01899 438088.Changes To This PolicyWe may change this privacy policy. Any changes to this privacy policy will apply to you and your data immediately.Last Updated: 14th June 2018Contact Us or Make a ComplaintContact the Data Protection Officer (DPO) if you: have any questions about anything in this document think that your personal data has been misused or mishandledPete Featherstone Email: hello@bigdecision.co.uk Telephone: 01899 438088 Mail: Big Decision. 1 Biggar Business Park, Market Road, Biggar, Lanarkshire,ML12 6FX. Website Production
Ecommerce
Digital Marketing×Business as UsualWe are open for business. Please contact us as normal during the lockdown on 01899 438088 or email hello@bigdecision.co.ukCloseAddress:1 Biggar Business Park, Market Road, Biggar Lanarkshire, ML12 6FXTelephone:01899 438088Email:hello@bigdecision.co.ukGet a QuoteFactsheetPay InvoiceWordPress Insights #1 read more >> We have been working on the web since 1999. We provide high-quality web sites, development, digital marketing and other online services to small and medium-sized businesses. Contact us today to discuss your project. Home | Sitemap | Privacy | Cookies
© Copyright 1999 -  Big Decision Ltd
